&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：我们谈论的第一个是函数内联。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: First one we talk
about is thisFunction Inlining.
这是我想指出的观点之一，有时你可以
And this is one of the ones where I want
to make the point that sometimes you can
四处移动代码，这并不重要，对吧？
go around moving around code and
it doesn't matter, right?
因为我们从优化编译器中学到的一件事就是
Because one of the things we've learned
from the optimizing compiler is just turn
不管怎么说你自己变成了机器代码。
yourself into machine code anyway.
您编写的代码并不总是V8执行的代码。
The code you write is not always
the code that V8 executes.
有时V8会继续为您重写代码，对吗？
Sometime V8 will go ahead and
rewrite your code for you, right?
因此，您的工作是使可读性最强、人类友好的代码成为可能。
So your job is to make the most readable,
human-friendly code possible.
V8的工作，也是Chrome团队的工作，就是让代码尽可能快地运行。
V8's job, and the Chrome team's job, is to
make that code run as fast as possible.
所以我们只看另一个简单的例子，
So we'll just look at
one other quick example,
然后我们就可以完成编译程序了，我向你保证。
and then we're done with compiler
land after that, I promise you.
你说，我喜欢编译器的土地，我现在住在这里。
You're like, I love compiler land,
I live here now.
[笑]酷
[LAUGH] Cool.
好的，让我们做一个代码方块，
All right, so
let's just make a code square,
它将需要一个数字和
and it will take a number and
它将返回x乘以x。
it will return x times x.
我们将创建另一个名为sumOfSquares的函数。
We'll make another one
called sumOfSquares.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那将需要一个a和a b，然后像方块a一样说，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: That will take an a and
a b, and say like square a,
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：加上b的平方，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: plus square of b,
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：sumOfSquares，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: sumOfSquares,
语法正确，是的。
grammatically correct, yeah.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我会说迭代，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I will say iteration,
迭代次数+1。
iterations + 1.
好的，我们继续说节点和
Okay, we'll go ahead and
we'll say node and
我们会说，基准。
we'll say, benchmark.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：大约花了8毫秒。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Took
about eight milliseconds.
现在，你会说，嘿，我必须做这个函数，我必须调用这个函数，
Now, you'll be like, hey, I had to make
this function, I gotta call this function,
这意味着编译器必须继续查找平方函数是什么，
which means the compiler has to go ahead
and look up what's the square function,
然后把东西传进去。
and pass the thing in.
我一直在听金科玉律
I've been listening to the golden rules,
我明白这样做应该比做这件事要慢。
I understand that doing that
should be slower than doing this.
a乘以a，b乘以b，看看这个。
a times a, b times b, look at that.
嘣，我现在要测量一下。
Boom, I'm gonna measure it now.
差不多一样。
It's like around the same.
对，就像我们两个都跑了几次。
Right, like we ran them both a few times.
他们在八点到十点左右徘徊。
They're hovering around eight to ten.
没什么不同。
It's no different.
真奇怪。
That's weird.
是不是应该像，Beckett的技术上比较慢。
Shouldn't it be like,
Beckett's was technically slower.
原来我们有一个叫做内联的东西。
Turns out we have this
thing called Inlining.
所以你做了跟踪涡轮内联(trace-turbo-inlining)。
So you do trace-turbo-inlining.
你就像什么涡轮内联？
You're like what is turbo inlining?
曲轴做了一种方式，涡轮风扇做了另一种方式。
Well crank shaft did it one way,
turbo fan does it another way.
所以这只是涡轮风扇的内联。
So it's just turbo fans inlining.
如果你去寻找跟踪内联，你什么都看不到，所以
You'll see nothing if you go looking for
trace inlining so
我们现在追踪涡轮内联。
we traced turbo-inlining now.
我就是其中之一，我已经报名了。
I for one, I'm signed up.
看，它正在将square内联到sumOfSquares中。
Look it's inlining square
into sumOfSquares.
所以你知道我之前做的那个很酷的优化，对吧？
So you know that cool
optimization I did before, right?
之前是8岁，这次是12岁，最后一次是10岁。
Before it was like 8, this time it was 12,
and the last time it was 10.
它看起来大致相同，就像针是这样来回移动的。
It looks like it's roughly the same, like
the needle goes back and forth like this.
所以发生的事情是Chrome就像，嘿，我必须继续调用这个函数。
So what happened was Chrome is like, hey,
I have to keep calling this function.
如果我只是把我们第一次所拥有的重写成第二次所拥有的呢？
What if I just rewrote what we had the
first time to what we had the second time?
它代表你做这件事。
And it does that for you on your behalf.
对，所以它会运行，它会看到您正在调用相同的函数，然后
Right, so it'll go and it sees you're
calling the same function over and
一次又一次，它基本上会重写你的代码
over and over again, it'll basically
go and rewrite your code so
你不能调用那个函数。
you're not calling that function.
好的，你不用担心这个，它会做到的，你得到它是为了
Right, you don't have to worry about this,
it'll just do it, you get it for
自由快乐的一天。
free, happy day.
你可以稍后再感谢本尼迪克特和弗朗西斯卡。
You can thank Benedict and
Francisca about that later.